lordcraft.com 2012-04-06

# :: World of Lordcraft :: Free Browser Games ::

#### 1\. Subject matter of this privacy policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all services which are offered on World of Lordcraft internet sites, in particular the World of Lord portal at 'www.worldoflordcraft.com' and the individual online game sites.

Unless stated otherwise, this Privacy Policy exclusively regulates how World of Lordcraft treats your personal information. If you make use of services provided by the third parties, the Privacy Policy conditions of these third parties apply. World of Lordcraft does not take responsibility for Privacy Policy conditions of the third parties.

#### 2\. Children's privacy practices of World of Lordcraft

The provision of World of Lordcraft Products to anyone under 18 years of age is not conditioned on the collection of more personal information than is reasonably necessary for participation. If we become aware that we hold or have inadvertently disclosed any personally identifiable information for any player aged under 13, it will be retroactively deleted from our system to ensure the protection of the child's privacy.

#### 3\. Collection of information

Generally, you can access our Internet without disclosing any personal information to us. It is always your choice whether or not to provide us with your personal information. We collect your information to be able to fulfill the user requirements. In addition to monitoring compliance with the terms and rules this includes, in particular, the proper handling of your payment arrangements.

If you would like to register on our Internet sites, participate in promotions or subscribe to our newsletter, it is necessary to provide personal information. This information includes, for example, your name, address, e-mail address and other personal information which World of Lordcraft may query in individual cases. In many cases it is possible to use World of Lordcraft's services by using pseudonyms. Users are encouraged to make use of this feature.

In addition, individual information such as IP address, browser type and access time will automatically be transferred to us by your computer and stored on our server. Except for the purpose of prosecuting unauthorized use of our website, we evaluate such information only for statistical and performance-related purposes. Where possible, the information is anonymized.

To make the visit to our Internet sites as pleasant as possible, we use, like many other companies, so-called cookies. After your visit to our website, these cookies are usually automatically deleted from your hard drive. Your Internet browser can be set to reject cookies generally. This can lead, for technical reasons, to restrict functioning of our Internet offerings.

We gather, process and use personal information – unless already permitted by statutes – only with your consent. If this consent is made in an electronic manner in the context of our online offerings, we shall fulfill the legal requirements to inform you of it.

#### 4\. Use of your personal information

We use your personal data in order to constantly improve our range of services to satisfy the user's needs. World of Lordcraft uses your personal information for the establishment, processing and settlement of your user relationship with World of Lordcraft and the processing of payments. Furthermore, we use your information in order to communicate with you. This includes that we, as the case may be, inform you about novelties of our services via e-mail. We use your personal information in order to inform you about products, services or certain events which could be of interest to you on a regular basis. You will be informed as part of this communication that you may cancel the subscription at any time. Finally, we use your information in order to protect our web pages and trace unauthorized accesses.

#### 5\. Transmission of personal information

As a matter of course, your data will not be sold to third parties. World of Lordcraft exclusively transmits your personal data to the following extent: We work together with payment providers (e.g. credit card companies, banks, PayPal, mobile services, debt collection agencies, etc.) and providers that create and compile statistical data, IT service providers (e.g. data centers, hosts, backup services, database services). These service providers only have access to your data to the extent which is necessary for the completion of their tasks. These service providers are obliged to treat your data according to this privacy policy and the relevant data protection statutes.

In the case that World of Lordcraft, subsidiary companies controlled by World of Lordcraft, particular affiliated companies or shares of the company are sold, your customer information will generally be passed on together with the transmitted part of the company. Of course, in this case your data is also subject to this privacy policy and the relevant data protection statutes.

#### 6\. Security of your personal information

We process the information collected from you according to United States data protection law. All employees are obliged and have been advised to maintain data confidentiality and privacy obligations.
